Guide to the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies records, 1966-2014 RL.11552
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Center Offices, 1969-2013
  - Office of Information Resources (OOR/Library), 1964-2013
    - OOR Subject files, 1972-2013
      - OOR TV violence, files, 1993-1995
        - Staff meeting minutes, 1994 Apr-Aug (Box 130)
        - Television violence and children project description, 1994 (Box 130)
        - TV violence and kids, notice letters, undated (Box 130)
        - Warriner, Doris, 1994 (Box 130)
        - West Coast trip, 1994 (Box 130)
        - Walls, Dwayne - The Chickenbone Special, 1970 Mar (Box 155)
        - A Review of Program Activities During 1971, 1972 Feb (Box 155)
        - An Analysis of Voting Patterns in Alabama and Georgia, 1984 (Box 155)
  - Office of Communications and Marketing (OCM), 1969-2013
    The Office of Communications and Marketing materials contain press releases, photographs, biographies and audiovisual materials used in outreach and reporting of the Joint Center's activities.
    - OCM Publicity, 1970-2007
      Includes publicity lapel pin and charms, press coverage on Joint Center activities, and photographs, profiles, resumes, and correspondence used for publicity outreach, and is arranged chronologically.
      - OCM press coverage, 1970-2007; 30 folders (Box 165)
        Includes news coverage, newsletters, and news clippings on Joint Center activities arranged chronologically.
      - JCPES Associates, 1983-2004; 10 folders (Box 170)
        includes materials on William A. Allen, Barry K. Campbell, Roger A. Campos, George E.Cave, Kenneth Chance, Gayla Cook, Lynn C. McNair, Robert Montjoy, and Togo West.
      - Williams, Eddie N., correspondence, 1989-2001; 7 folders (Box 170)
        includes correspondence, headshots, memorandums, speeches, op-eds, and awards used as press materials related to Eddie N. Williams.
      - Memorandums, Office of Communications to Office of the President, 1998 (Box 170)
      - Census and Reapportionment in the 1990's, Carnegie proposal, 1988 (Box 170)
      - Administrative assistant job description, 1980s (Box 170)
      - Artifact, Joint Center lapel pins, charm, 2000s; 3 folders (Box 201)
        Includes three silvertone lapel pins, one gold tone lapel pin, and one sterling silver charm.
    - Documentary film proposals, transcripts, correspondence, and notes, 1986-1991
      Contains materials related to documentary film projects sponsored by the center on topics such as drug abuse, African Americans and the Constitution, public affairs, and urban youth. The budgets, proposals, transcripts, correspondence, and notes pertaining to these productions are arranged in chronological order.
      - PBS proposal, Hopkins School of Public Health, 1986-1988 (Box 170)
      - A Tradition of Giving video, 1987-1988 (Box 170)
      - FOCUS, production, 1987-1988 (Box 170)
      - Afro-Americans and the Living Constitution, 1988; 2 folders (Box 170)
      - Blacks and the Constitution production, 1988 (Box 170)
      - Black Philanthropy and Volunteerism, documentary film, 1988 (Box 170)
      - Meeting the Challenge, 1988 (Box 170)
      - Documentary notes and correspondence, 1988-1989; 4 folders (Box 170)
      - Public Affairs Television, pilot series, 1988-1989 (Box 170)
      - Radio America, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 170)
      - Turning It Around, 1988-1989 (Box 170)
      - Project Discovery, Alexandria, 1989 (Box 170)
      - The Voter's Channel, proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 170)
      - A Black American/Japanese forum, proposal, 1991 (Box 170)
      - The '92 Campaign and Black America, radio series proposal, 1991 (Box 170)
      - Philadelphia conference on Urban Drug Abuse, video, undated (Box 170)
      - Lloyd, Mark - documentary proposals, 1989-1991 (Box 181)
    - OCM Photographs, 1969-2009
      This subseries includes photographs of events, staff and associates created to promote the activities of the Joint Center and are grouped by media.
      - OCM Photographs: Conferences, events, meetings, 1969-2006
        This subseries includes photographs of conferences, events, and meetings.
        - Press conference for the Institute for Responsible Fatherhood, 1995 Jun 15 (Box 129)
        - Digital Divide photographs, 1999 Oct 19 (Box 129)
          Includes images of James Casey, S. Keith Fulton, and Eddie Williams.
        - Youth Leadership Development program, 1980 (Box 129)
        - OMBE and National Conference of Black Mayors, undated (Box 129)
          Includes images of Dr. Randolph T. Blackwell.
        - Poverty conference, Moynihan lunch, 1987 (Box 129)
        - Poverty conference, Moynihan lunch negatives, 1987 (Box 129)
        - Conference on Industrial Policy, 1983 Oct 14-15 (Box 129)
        - Education conference and ENW Award, 1990 May 8 (Box 129)
          Includes images of Judge Thompson.
        - South African conference, undated (Box 129)
        - Philadelphia Drug conference negatives, 1990 Oct 22-23 (Box 129)
        - Leadership conference forum, undated (Box 129)
        - Conference pictures - group, 1986 (Box 129)
        - White House conference negatives, 1990 Mar 15 (Box 129)
        - NBC LEO meeting, undated (Box 129)
        - Research department meeting negatives, 1984 (Box 129)
        - Forum on Career Advancement in the Military, Advisory committee to HUD Privatization project, 1984 May (Box 129)
        - Forum on Career Advancement in the Military, Advisory committee to HUD Privatization project negatives, 1984 May (Box 129)
        - Election press briefing, 1982 (Box 129)
        - I.C.A. meetings, undated (Box 129)
        - Economic task force, undated (Box 129)
        - Economic task force negatives, undated (Box 129)
        - Roundtable on the Future of Public Hospitals, 1997 Mar 7 (Box 129)
          Includes images of Charlotte Collins, and Bailus Walker.
        - New York state Affirmative Action Advisory Council's training symposium, 1995 (Box 129)
          Includes images of Margaret Simms.
        - Wall Street Journal conference, Black Entrepreneurship in America, 1995 Oct 19-20 (Box 129)
        - Brown Bag, undated (Box 129)
          Includes images of Elliott Skinner.
        - Tenth anniversary annual meeting and conference of the National Association of Securities professionals, 1995 Sep 22 (Box 129)
        - Aetna roundtable contact sheets, 1993 Jun 10 (Box 129)
        - American Sociological conference, 1995 Aug (Box 129)
          Includes images of Yvonne Scruggs.
        - Black Appointee reception, undated (Box 129)
        - Somalia roundtable contact sheets, 1993 Jul (Box 129)
        - Forum on the growing influence of the Congressional Black Caucus, 2006 Oct 18 (Box 129)
          Includes images of Bill Clinton.
        - Military forum, 1998 May 20 (Box 129)
        - Congressional Black Caucus forum, 1998 Sep 18 (Box 129)
        - Health forum, undated (Box 129)
        - Impact of Medicaid Managed Care on African Americans, 1997 Nov 13 (Box 129)
          Includes images of Frederic Leigh, Ron Tallon, and Eddie Williams.
        - Future of Public Hospitals, 1997 Oct 15 (Box 131)
        - Devolution and Welfare reform, 1997 Nov 12 (Box 131)
          Includes images of Eddie Williams, Yvonne Scruggs, Sullivan Robinson, Margaret Simms, and Arnold Tompkins.
        - Conference on Job Creation, 1997 Apr 8 (Box 131)
          Includes images of Rep. William Jefferson, Franklin Raines, and Eddie Williams.
        - National Opinion Poll on race relations/children's issues, 1997 Jun 17 (Box 131)
          Includes images of David Bositis, Eddie Williams, William Winter, and Yvonne Scruggs.
        - Redistricting, 1997 Jan 9 (Box 131)
        - Black males conference, undated (Box 131)
          Includes images of Chief Fred Thomas.
        - Forum on Managed Care's Impact, undated (Box 131)
          Includes images of Karen Scott Collins, Arnold Epstein, and Sylvia Drew Ivie, and other unidentified people
        - Alternative service delivery meeting and brown bag lunch on Black Delegation to Israel negatives, 1985 Apr (Box 131)
        - Underclass conference, 1990 Mar 8 (Box 131)
        - Department of Justice news conference on Drug Precaution initiative, 1991 Aug 3 (Box 131)
        - Philadelphia Drug conference, 1990 Oct 23 (Box 131)
        - Distinguished scholars meeting errata and reprints, 1987 Jan (Box 131)
        - Department of Justice conference, 1991 (Box 132)
        - Health care conference, 1992 (Box 132)
        - Leadership discussion series with Dr. Vivian Penn, 1992 (Box 132)
          Includes images of Dr. Vivian Penn, Roger Wilkins, and Eddie Williams.
        - International poverty conference, undated (Box 132)
          Includes images of Dr. Sullivan.
        - Black leadership meeting, blacks in the military, Anna Perez event, 1976; 1991 (Box 132)
          Includes images of Gerald Ford.
        - Southern Conference of Black Mayors, undated (Box 132)
        - Blacks in the military, 1991 Jun 26 (Box 132)
        - Healthcare conference, Brown bag, Minority issues Japan, undated (Box 132)
        - Roundtable, 1987 (Box 132)
        - Minority business conference institute contact prints, undated (Box 132)
        - Conference Nationwide, undated (Box 132)
        - Conference Nationwide negatives, undated (Box 132)
        - Black leadership forum, undated (Box 132)
        - JCPS Advisory conference; Jesse meets the press at Black leadership council, 1972; 1988 (Box 132)
          Includes images of Jesse Jackson.
        - HBO/JC voter poll results and leadership discussion, 1992 (Box 132)
        - Minority Set-aside conference, 1986 Sep 17 (Box 132)
        - White House reception, 1969; 3 folders (Box 132)
          Includes images of Richard Nixon.
        - Unlabeled seminar/roundtable, undated (Box 132)
        - Unknown conference negatives, undated (Box 132)
        - Photograph photocopies, 1976-2009 (Box 173)
          Includes images of Bill Clinton, John Lewis, Coretta Scott King, Jesse Jackson, and Muhammad Ali.
        - Events and headshots, 2013; undated (Box 173)
          Includes images of Forum on Economic Policy lunch, Lt. Gov. Betsy McCaughey Ross, Eddie Williams, and Edwin Dorn.
        - Unlabeled negatives, undated (Box 173)
        - Unidentified meeting, undated (Box 173)
        - Unidentified meeting, undated (Box 173)
          Includes images of Bill Clinton, and Jesse Jackson.
        - Unidentified events, offices, undated; 2 folders (Box 173)
        - Unidentified events, offices - negatives, undated; 2 folders (Box 173)
        - Unidentified events, undated (Box 173)
          Includes images of Shirley Chisholm.
        - Unidentified events - negatives, undated (Box 173)
        - The National Coalition on Black Civic Participation, undated (Box 173)
        - Zakharon meeting, Indonesia meeting, 1999 Apr 15 (Box 173)
        - Diverging Generations, 2001 Jun 21 (Box 173)
          Includes images of Margaret Simms, David Bostis, William Spriggs, and Winnett Hagens.
        - Meetings and staff, 1992-1997 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Al Gore, Jesse Jackson, Elaine Jones, Ron Brown, Eddie Williams, and Louis Sullivan.
        - Health Conference, 1992 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Rashidah Hassan, Louis Stokes, Calvine Johnson, Kevin Moley, Ballus Walker, David Sundwall, and Eddie Williams.
        - Barbara Jordan, Charlie Rangel, undated (Box 174)
        - Civil Rights Conference, negatives, undated (Box 174)
        - Spencer Holland at Young Black Males Conference, 1993 (Box 174)
        - Film premiere opening for documentary on US Black/Japanese Relations, 1993 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Regge Life, and Paige Cottingham.
        - Strapped Actor Roundtable, 1993 Jun 17 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Forest Whitaker.
        - CPRJ Press Conference, 1993 Sep 13 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Eddie Williams, Doug Wilder, John Hope Franklin, Roger Wilkins, and Mary Frances Berry.
        - Argrett reception, 1993 Dec (Box 174)
        - South Africa Project briefing, 1993 Dec 21 (Box 174)
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Terrence Devernay, undated (Box 174)
        - Freedom forum, undated (Box 174)
          Includes images of Katherine McFate.
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Maggie Williams, 1994 (Box 174)
        - Meeting participants, 1994 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Terrence Devernay.
        - Health conference, 1994 (Box 174)
        - National Rainbow Coalition Session on Violence, 1994 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Jesse Jackson, and Lee Brown.
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Togo West, 1994 (Box 174)
        - Foreign Aid Roundtable Discussion, 1994 (Box 174)
        - Leadership Discussion Series, reception, dinner, 1994; 1999-2001 (Box 174)
          Includes images of Robert Reich, and Al Gore.
        - Forum on the Growing Influence of the Congressional Black Caucus, 1994 (Box 174)
          Includes images of David Bostis, Eddie Williams, Lon Walls, Donald Payne, and Sonia Jarvis.
        - National Rainbow Coalition Summit on Black on Black Crime and Youth Violence, 1994 Jan 7 (Box 175)
          Includes images of Jesse Jackson, C. Delores Tucker, Isaac Fulwood, Al Sharpton, and Lee Brown.
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Sheldon Hackney, 1994 Apr 18 (Box 175)
        - US-Japan Project Black-Japanese Luncheon, 1994 Apr 27 (Box 175)
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Robert Reich, 1994 May 18 (Box 175)
        - Health conference, David Satcher, 1994 May 26 (Box 175)
        - Black Males conference, contact sheets, 1994 Jun 6 (Box 175)
        - Executive Leadership conference, Andrew Young, 1994 Jul 23; 2 folders (Box 175)
        - US Peacekeeping Policy Symposium, 1994 Oct 19 (Box 175)
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Hazel O'Leary, 1994 Aug 11 (Box 175)
          Includes images of Eleanor Farrar, Frederic Leigh, Jayne Ikard, and Yvonne Scruggs.
        - Black Leadership forum, 1994 Dec (Box 175)
        - Lead Discussion Series, Deval Patrick, 1995 Jan 25 (Box 176)
        - Library of Congress event, 1995 Feb 15 (Box 176)
          Includes images of Warren Thompson, Robert L. Wallace, Alden McDonald, and Eddie Williams.
        - Census, Joint Center Press conference, 1995 Feb 22 (Box 176)
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Henry Cisneros, 1995 Mar 2 (Box 176)
        - Forum on Youth Resident Home in Israel, Zvi Levi, 1995 Jun 5 (Box 176)
        - Health briefing, In the Nation's Interest: The Quest for Health Equity, 1995 Sep 18 (Box 176)
          Includes images of Eddie Bernice Johnson, Karen Davis, Donna Willis, Marsha Ullie-Blanton, and Louis Stokes.
        - Health Committee meeting, 1996 (Box 176)
          Includes images of Vivian W. Pinn.
        - National Opinion Poll, 1996 Feb 21 (Box 176)
        - Swedish Labor representatives, 1996 Mar 5 (Box 176)
          Includes images of Margaret Simms, Anders Sundstrom, Bjorn Jonzon, Peter Akinder, and Gote Bernhardsson.
        - Memphis forum on HIV/AIDS among African American Youth: Developing an Action Agenda for Leaders and Policymakers, 1996 Mar 6 (Box 176)
        - National Newspaper Publisher Association meeting, Diane Powers, 1996 Mar 14 (Box 176)
        - Military Roundtable Discussion on Hate Groups in the Military, 1996 Apr 11 (Box 176)
        - Military Seminar on the Status of Minorities in the Changing Military, 1996 May 6 (Box 176)
          Includes images of Don Baker.
        - Domestic Violence Workshop, South Africa, 1996 May 17 (Box 176)
          Includes images of Judge Elsa Lamelas, Marshall Murray, Kathi Stolpman, Dolly Grimes-Johnson, and Howard Linstedt.
        - Fundraiser, Anna Deavere Smith, 1997 (Box 176)
        - Corporate Leadership forum, 1999 (Box 177)
          Includes images of Alexis Herman, Judge Joyce London Alexander, Robert Johnson, Brenda Joel, Cecelia Conrad, Margaret Simms, Wendell Freeland, Carolyn Henderson-Tyson, Mel Farr, and Albert Siu.
        - Leadership Discussion Series, Ron Brown, 1999 (Box 177)
        - Community News on Tape, South Africa, 1999 (Box 177)
          Includes images of Eve Thompson, and Joe Mogashoa.
        - Urban Agenda Roundtable, negatives, 1999 Apr 15-16; 2 folders (Box 177)
        - Social Security meeting, 1999 Apr 21 (Box 177)
          Includes images of Rudolph Penner, and Samuel Beard.
        - Military forum, Underrepresentation of Hispanic Army Officers, 1999 May 18 (Box 177)
        - BLIE DataBank Presentation, 1999 Oct 13 (Box 177)
          Includes images of Dorothy Height.
        - Digital Divide, 1999 Oct 19 (Box 177)
          Includes images of Larry Irving, B. Keith Fulton, George Campbell, Jr., Charles Rangel, and Bruce Lincoln.
        - Skills Development, 1999 Nov 3 (Box 177)
        - Moonlight Cabaret, 1999 Nov 10 (Box 177)
          Includes images of Al Gorek and Jesse Jackson.
        - Moonlight Cabaret, 2000 (Box 178)
        - White House visit, Liselle Yorke, 2000 (Box 178)
        - HIV/AIDS Forum, 2000 Jan 20 (Box 178)
        - FreddieMac/LaSalle Street Project, Jesse Jackson, 2000 Apr 14; 2 folders (Box 178)
        - Maryland Business Roundtable (MBRT) CEO Workshop, 2000 Sep 26 (Box 178)
          Includes images of Robert Mallett, Gregory L. Craig, Robert Hatcher, Donald Lee, and Eddie Williams.
        - National Opinion Poll, 2000 Oct 23 (Box 178)
        - Maryland Business Roundtable (MBRT) and Congressional briefing, 2001 Jan 17 (Box 178)
          Includes images of Roger Campos, Rodney Azama, Albert Chen, Betty Monetta, Wallace Tsuha, Ruth Sandoval, Howard Li, Kwame Brown, Gregory Craig, Audra Rush, Mark La, Margaret Simms, and Eddie Williams.
        - Untitled meeting, 2001 Apr 6 (Box 178)
        - HIV/AIDS Workshop, negatives, 2001 Apr 2; 2 folders (Box 178)
        - Maryland Business Roundtable (MBRT) meeting, Ronald M. Langston, 2001 Apr 25 (Box 178)
        - Reception, Weldon Latham and John Conyers, 2001 Jun 7 (Box 178)
        - Dispelling the Myths forum, 2003 Jul 10 (Box 178)
        - Event on Martha's Vineyard, 2004 (Box 178)
        - Events, meetings, and conferences, 1970s-2000s; 34 folders (Box 186)
        - Events, meetings, and conferences, 1990s; 7 folders (Box 187)
        - Staff, meetings, 1970s-1980s; 15 folders (Box 188)
        - Staff, meetings, 1980s-1990s; 19 folders (Box 189)
      - OCM Photographs: Offices and staff, 1979-2002
        This subseries is arranged chronologically and includes photographs of staff and associates.
        - Joint Center lobby design, undated (Box 179)
        - Christmas party, negatives, 1979-1983; 1986; 1988; 12 folders (Box 179)
        - Christmas party, 1991; 1992; 2 folders (Box 179)
        - Interns, Tara Lehman and Ian Lehman, 1993 (Box 179)
        - Ford Conference Center, 1994 (Box 179)
        - Interns, 1994 (Box 179)
        - Book display, negatives, 1994 Jul 26-28; 2 folders (Box 179)
        - Strategic Plan review, 1994 Jan 13 (Box 179)
        - Sustained Superior Performance Awards reception, 1994 Apr 22 (Box 179)
        - Reception, Ron Johnson and Von Lipsey, 1995 Jun 27 (Box 179)
        - Interns, 1996 (Box 179)
        - Holiday party, 1997-2001; 5 folders (Box 179)
        - Summer picnic, negatives, 2000-2001; 3 folders (Box 179)
        - Interns, 2001 Jul 13 (Box 179)
        - Retreat, 2002 Jun (Box 179)
        - Annual report photographs, graphics, 1980s-1990s; 18 folders (Box 194)
        - Annual report photographs, graphics, 1980s-1990s; 10 folders (Box 195)
        - Publications photographs, graphics, 1980s-1990s; 12 folders (Box 196)
          Includes images used in Louis Martin biography, Walking with Presidents.
      - OCM Photographs: Group and headshots, 1970s-2000s
        This subseries is arranged chronologically and includes photographs of staff and associates created to promote the activities of the Joint Center.
        - Individuals and groups, A-C, 1970s-2000s; 68 folders (Box 190)
          Includes images of Muhammad Ali, Yvonne Burke, Bill Clinton, and Kenneth B. Clark.
        - Individuals and groups, E-J, 1970s-2000s; 62 folders (Box 191)
          Includes images of Julian Dixon, Mervyn Dymally, Eleanor Farrar, George Foreman, John Hope Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Maynard Jackson, and Vernon Jordan.
        - Individuals and groups, K-V, 1970s-2000s; 55 folders (Box 192)
          Includes images of Sharon Pratt Kelly, Martin Luther King III, Coretta Scott King, Katherine McFate, Margaret Simms, and Kathleen Vander Horst.
        - Individuals and groups, W-Y, 1970s-2000s; 8 folders (Box 193)
          Includes images of Doug Wilder, and Andrew Young.
        - Williams, Eddie N., 1960s-2000s; 26 folders (Box 193)
          Includes images on scrapbook pages.
        - Photocopies of photographs, 1960s-2000s; 4 folders (Box 197)
          Includes images of John F. Kennedy, Lyndon Johnson, Dorothy Height, Jesse Jackson, Bill Clinton, John Lewis, Vernon Jordan, and Eddie N. Williams.
        - Slides, people and events, 1970s-1980s; 2 folders (Box 197)
          Includes images of Andrew Young.
        - Events, 1970s-1980s; 11 folders (Box 198)
          Includes images of Energy and Equity event, Eddie N. Williams, conference in Africa.
        - Events, 1980s-2000s; 11 folders (Box 199)
          Includes images of Al Gore, Eddie N. Williams, John Hope Franklin, Hillary Clinton, Colin Powell, an event in Africa, and a golf event.
        - Staff, headshots, graphic, historic reproductions, 1980s-2000s; 6 folders (Box 200)
          Includes images of Eddie N. Williams, Charles Rangel, Barbara Jordan, Ron Brown, staff parties, and publicity graphics.
      - OCM Graphics, scrapbook pages, 1989-1994
        This subseries includes FOCUS magazine graphics, and oversize scrapbook pages with photographs arranged chronologically.
        - FOCUS Magazine, advertisements, 1994; undated (Box 183)
        - Williams, Eddie N. and Wendell Freeland, 1991 (Box 183)
        - Arnold, Major General Wallace, brown bag lunch, 1992 (Box 183)
        - Meeting with South Africans at JCPES, 1989 (Box 183)
        - Meeting with South Africans at JCPES, negatives, 1989 (Box 183)
        - CPRJ, Ms. Lunder, undated (Box 183)
        - Jones, Senator Roxanne H., FOCUS Magazine, 1982 (Box 183)
        - Annual Report, contact sheets, 1991-1992 (Box 183)
        - Kearns, David, Jalapa Ineges, and Dwayne Freeman, 1992 Feb 12 (Box 183)
        - CPRI Meeting with Dr. Sarah Lightfoot, 1992 Jan (Box 184)
        - Lightfoot, Sarah Lawrence, undated (Box 184)
        - Lightfoot, Sarah Lawrence, negatives, undated (Box 184)
        - Drug Enforcement Roundtable, undated (Box 184)
        - Drug Enforcement Roundtable, negatives, undated (Box 184)
        - Bruno, Hal, 1992 Feb 28 (Box 184)
        - Sullivan briefing, Secretary of U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1992 Feb 5 (Box 184)
        - Jordan, Emma, brown bag lunch on sexual harassment, 1992 Nov 13 (Box 184)
        - Economic Policy Task Force, Derrick Bell lecture, undated (Box 184)
        - Annual Report, contact sheets, 1989 (Box 184)
        - Minorities and Privatization, cover (Box 184)
        - Minorities and Privatization, cover negatives, undated (Box 184)
        - Eco Policy forum, undated (Box 184)
        - Eco Policy forum, negatives, undated (Box 184)
        - International forum on Africa, 1991 (Box 184)
        - Blacks and the Constitution filming, Louis Sullivan, HHS Secretary, Civil Rights Conference and dinner, undated (Box 184)
        - Blacks and the Constitution filming, Louis Sullivan, HHS Secretary, Civil Rights Conference and dinner, negatives, undated (Box 184)
        - Furtrell, Mary, 1992 Feb 19 (Box 184)